sup everyone tables under your Fath it
was a very special video today now
you're not gonna believe this I was
cleaning my closet and if you like
make room for soccer I'm collection
and I got came across this Hot Wheels
tour now I don't know what the is
box called hog was mystery
so I'm guessing if I open it it's going
like some weird-ass color like a random
like Oh as I see it like whatever color
is it'll match the song character sorry
about like this poop saying I don't know
what the that is a my anyways mama
mama turn up turn down Cupcake Wars
I tried to phone a video mama
turn down Cupcake Wars
Johnny give me your ass down
I'll be a ass gotta put got
four in the place tomorrow
now how about we open this see
what's like on calculus do this now I'll
just say this if I don't get blue or
yellow
I might just punch y'all's mama beat
your ass can't get this
open King get the
mama open up open up oh man mama oh yeah
oh he'll go I won't boom what the
are you cheating me days why
it's for that's not some character what
the is this a mama what do you mean
I should be grateful dude you
should be grateful I'll beat your ass
[Applause]
I don't want that what the
it said this was gonna be a myth it
said this was gonna be a mystery caller
what is this oh my God what can I play
with this
[Applause]